{
    "subject": "resource/Arnold_Schwarzenegger",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
    "human_readable": "The name of Arnold Schwarzenegger is Arnold Schwarzenegger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9645780324935913,
            "question": "What is the full name of Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9478216171264648,
            "question": "Is there a nickname associated with Arnold Schwarzenegger's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9437058568000793,
            "question": "Is Arnold Schwarzenegger's name different from his given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9426009058952332,
            "question": "What name is most commonly used to refer to Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9403784871101379,
            "question": "Is Arnold Schwarzenegger a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8190006613731384,
            "question": "How would you write Arnold Schwarzenegger's name formally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8042022585868835,
            "question": "Can you tell me Arnold Schwarzenegger's first and last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7602180242538452,
            "question": "How would you pronounce Arnold Schwarzenegger's name correctly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7553046941757202,
            "question": "What is the order of Arnold Schwarzenegger's name components?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.734241783618927,
            "question": "Does Arnold Schwarzenegger have any other names he goes by?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Arnold Schwarzenegger is Arnold Schwarzenegger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8418_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the order of Arnold Schwarzenegger's name components?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8418_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you pronounce Arnold Schwarzenegger's name correctly?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8418_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Arnold Schwarzenegger's first and last name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8418_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8418_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various biographical details about Arnold Schwarzenegger, including his full name, which matches the statement \"The name of Arnold Schwarzenegger is Arnold Schwarzenegger.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}